

I'm passionate about technology, science, developing things that improve people's lives and make the world a better place. I've been working with mobile development for iOS platform since 2014 with experience on all steps of iOS development, from the concept ofthe ideas until releasing the app on the store and following the results with analytics, tests and crashreports.

EXPERIENCE

IOS DEVELOPER **▼ PAGSEGURO UOL**

July 2018 - March 2021, Working with native applications using Swift

FREELANCER IOS DEVELOPER ▼ **STORMBREAKER STUDIOS**

January 2020 - December 2020, Working in iOS applications using Swift

IOS DEVELOPER **▼ BRQ**

April 2017 - June 2018, Working with native applications using Swift and Objective-C

IOS DEVELOPER ▼ MAGNA SISTEMAS

February 2016 - April 2017, Working with native applications using Swift...

IOS DEVELOPER **▼ URBAN SUMMER**

March 2015 - February 2016, Working with native and hybrid mobile Apps...

EDUCATION

SYSTEM ANALYSIS AND DEVELOPMENT

Learning algorithms, software engineer, databases, software development in FMU, Sao Paulo, Brazil

IOS DEVELOPER

Learning a lot of concepts about iOS development in Impacta, Sao Paulo, Brazil

SKILLS

- > Xcode
- > Obj-C
- > MVVM
- > (|
- > SPM
- > Auto Layout
- > Framework Building

- > Swift
- > git
- > MVC
- cocoapods
- > Tests
- > Agile Methodologies